

DEEP KAWALE

DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Courteous and enthusiastic, I am interested in Full Stack Development and everything in it's orbit, have experience in collaborative programming. I am currently at my inital stage of learning new technologies, trying to give my best so that i can have all the potential to rise in this huge IT field.

CORE SKILLS

- C
- C++
- Java
- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MERN
- Android [Java]
- .NET
- MySQL
- Oracle

REACH ME AT:

Email: kawaledeep@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <u>@Deepkk-9</u> Github: <u>@Deepkk-9</u>

Address: Alibaug-Raigad, India 402-201

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Holy Family Convent School

• SSC-Primary | 2009 - 2012

St. Mary's Convent School

• SSC-Secondary | 2012 - 2020

Pillai HOC Polytechnic

• Diploma in Computer Science | 2019 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern

C-Tech Continentals | Aug 2021 - present

- Delivered an Agile web based service for managing events.
- Developed an E-commerce Application for Android.

Co-lead

Pillai's Developer Community | Jul 2013 - Dec 2014

• Managed and contributed to many web-based projects.

PROJECTS

- Python Discord Bot who motivates you and crack's joke to make you feel lively again after recognizing sad msgs from you.
- Python Personal Assistant who has many features from searching in google to playing music or videos by just recognizing voice.
- Android Calculator with great UI.
- · A web service which provides efficient event handling.
- An E-commerce app to make day-to-day life easier!